Guide to the Craig Wirth broadcast journalism audio-visual collection 1903-1990s, bulk 1950s-1990s
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- 2002 addendum
  - (Box 60)
    - 4 posters, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1814)
    - Salt Palace, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1815)
    - Seniors jam session, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1816)
    - Lagoon interview and still photos, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1817)
    - Moms 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1818)
    - Senile seashells 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1819)
    - Ice berg 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1820)
    - Wirth standups, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1821)
    - Library B-roll and Wirth standup, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1822)
    - Charles, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1823)
    - Ice skating, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1824)
    - Salt 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1825)
    - Merry-go-round 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1826)
    - Trolley, 1999 June 10; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1827)
    - Old Main, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1828-1829)
    - Standups, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1830)
    - Tap 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1831)
    - Internet 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1832)
    - Phoenix, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1833-1834)
    - Traffic, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1835)
    - Gawk 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1836)
    - Recycle, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1837)
    - Car in Calgary, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1838)
    - Paul track, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1839)
    - Hold DJ, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1840)
    - Clarion 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1841)
    - Ida Tataeoka interview, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1842)
    - Skate Liberty Park, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1843)
    - Tree man, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1844)
    - Halloween farm, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1845)
    - Capitol, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1846)
    - Tower 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1847)
    - Dust bowl 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1848)
    - Park City fire 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1849)
  - (Box 61)
    - Cooking class, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1850)
    - Old train movie, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1851)
    - Ping pong 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1852)
    - Pet resort 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1853)
    - Red Butte 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1854)
    - Fathers, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1855-1856)
    - Old mill 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1857)
    - Blind, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1858)
    - Tonight show, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1859)
    - Gardner Mill 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1860)
    - Red Cross 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1861)
    - Wellers Macey 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1862)
    - Nordstrom, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1863-1864)
    - 99 history of television photos, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1865)
    - Auction 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1866)
    - Johnson Canyon 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1867)
    - Lewis and Clark 19, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1868)
    - Air dam 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1869)
    - Old skiers, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1870)
    - Dino dial, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1871-1872)
    - Clean 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1873)
    - My car, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1874)
    - License plates, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1875)
    - Chores, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1876)
    - Spinner, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1877)
    - McPearson 9, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1878)
    - Jazz photo 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1879)
    - Air 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1880)
    - Flashcard words, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1881)
    - Vince's barbershop, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1882)
    - Checker Cab, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1883)
    - Woolers money, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1884)
    - Unidentified videocassette, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1885)
    - Marbles 1, 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1886-1887)
    - Marble HZ, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1888)
    - Infomercial, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1889-1890)
    - Red Butte track, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1891)
    - St. George opera, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1892-1893)
    - Wirth infomercial, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1894)
    - Flood; Los Angeles, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1895)
    - Trax opera house, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1896)
    - Media link 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1897)
    - Holland Lake, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1898)
    - Twinkies of Ogden, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1899)
    - Revere 11, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1900)
    - Revere music, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1901)
    - Revere, Adams 13, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1902)
    - Revere and Old North Church, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1903)
    - Revere capture site, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1904)
  - (Box 62)
    - Revere - Long Fellow House, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1905)
    - House 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1906)
    - Paul Revere house 18, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1907)
    - Revere - Lexington, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1908)
    - Adams, Revere 10, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1909)
    - Hostess, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1910)
    - Stamp, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1911-1913)
    - Revere 12, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1914)
    - Twinkies 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1915)
    - Marbles tape 1 dub, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1916)
    - Tomorrow Land, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1917)
    - Media link Sears, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1918)
    - Lincoln Highway, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1919)
    - Beaver courthouse, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1920)
    - Wirth, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1921)
    - Cooking class, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1922)
    - St. Ann's, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1923-1924)
    - Rairoad, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1925)
    - Sears standup, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1926)
    - American Football League (AFL), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1927)
    - School 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1927)
    - Floralie Mill saps, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1928)
    - Salt harvest pictures, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1929)
    - High school graduation, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1930)
    - Monks, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1931-1933)
    - Park City mine, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1934)
    - Salt Lake Trappers baseball, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1935)
    - Billboards, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1936-1937)
    - Pig poet, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1938)
    - Lincoln, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1939-1940)
    - Rug, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1941)
    - Road tour - salt harvest, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1942)
    - Deer Valley, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1943)
    - Redmond Salt, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1944)
    - Hotel 5, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1945)
    - Downtown 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1946)
    - Hat 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1947)
    - Monument, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1948)
    - Cap downtown Salt Lake City, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1949)
    - Mill, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1950)
    - War footage, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1951)
    - 50th anniversary background, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1952)
    - Gerber photo shoot, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1953)
    - Floralie Mill saps 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1954)
    - Mary Black, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1955)
    - CNBC: Old mill, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1956)
    - Service station, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1957)
    - Sanders standups and B-roll, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1958)
    - Mary, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1959)
    - Goshen MKL, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1960)
    - Gart Sports, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1961)
  - (Box 63)
    - Alan Frank, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1962)
    - Antelope 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1963)
    - Nats River, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1964)
    - Breweries B-roll, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1965)
    - Weather 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1966)
    - Helper Christmas, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1967)
    - Library 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1968)
    - Park still photos, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1969)
    - Marcroft 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1970)
    - Prom 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1971)
    - Dandy Hogerus, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1972)
    - Redmond Salt, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1973)
    - World War II pilots, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1974)
    - Wendover 3 dub, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1975)
    - Pig poet, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1976)
    - Unidentified videocassette, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1977)
    - Horse whispering 8, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1978)
    - Larry H. Miller, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1979)
    - Monument Valley 10, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1980)
    - Bell special effects, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1981)
    - Pow, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1982)
    - Harvest 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1983)
    - Tape for Quince, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1984)
    - Snappy 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1985)
    - Standups 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1986)
    - Old machines 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1987)
    - Salt 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1988)
    - Parks interviews 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1989)
    - Airplane station, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1990-1991)
    - Parowan farms, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1992)
    - Dandy Hogerus 12, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1993)
    - Prom 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1994)
    - Marcroft 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1995)
    - Marysvale Old Pine pictures, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1996)
    - Wendover 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1997)
    - Lagoon 16, 5, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 1998-1999)
    - Horse whisperer 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2000)
    - Old Pine 2, 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2001-2002)
    - Wheeler Halloween 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2003)
    - Craig Wirth piece, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2004)
    - Sunspot, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2005)
    - Packard shoot, 1999 January; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2006)
    - Historical Society pictures, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2007)
    - Rhonda Shear 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2008)
    - Deer Valley, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2009)
    - Mark Eaton, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2010-2011)
    - Schindler, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2012-2013)
    - Dub for KTVX A, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2014)
    - Robert Poll interview, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2015)
    - Wendover 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2016)
    - NBC 20 years, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2017)
    - Wirth 9, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2018)
    - National Collegiate Athletics Association (NCAA) Final Four 2, 1966; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2019)
    - Old Ballet photos, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2020)
    - Kennecott, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2021)
    - Dust bowl 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2022)
    - Horse whisperer 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2023)
    - Dub of Wirth piece, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2024)
    - Statue standup, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2025)
    - Pow 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2026)
    - Thayne, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2027)
    - Eccles buildings, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2028)
    - Audio dish, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2029)
    - Rail 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2030)
    - Snow with mountains beauty shot, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2031)
    - Prison A, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2032)
    - Billboard hanging 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2033)
    - Fair play 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2034)
    - Glacier National Park, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2035)
    - Lagoon lemon, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2036)
  - (Box 64)
    - Browning, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2037)
    - Pow 1and 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2038-2039)
    - Car tips, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2040)
    - Toy town, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2041)
    - Horse whisperer 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2042)
    - Wesley's audio, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2043)
    - Rail 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2044)
    - Turkey 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2045)
    - 30 M, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2046-2048)
    - Park City station, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2049-2050)
    - B-25 bomber, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2051)
    - Avalon, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2052)
    - Famous Footsteps, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2053)
    - Wirth demo tape, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2054)
    - Jeri Cartwright's bloopers, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2055)
    - Roy Gibson 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2056)
    - Prom, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2057)
    - Midvale 1and 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2058-2059)
    - Car tape A, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2060)
    - Ann Graham Ehringer, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2061)
    - B-17 bomber, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2062)
    - Utah vs. BYU track, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2063)
    - Midvale Trax, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2064)
    - Rock of Fame; Rock Walk, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2065)
    - Helper, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2066-2067)
    - United Parcel Service (UPS) feed, 1997 August 12; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2068)
    - Cars B, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2069)
    - FNN promo reel, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2070)
    - Peter tape, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2071)
    - Movie 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2072)
    - Saltair broadcast cassette dub, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2073)
    - Brine shrimp, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2074)
    - Carnival of Souls; Brine shrimp, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2075)
    - Craig Wirth's old special 13, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2076)
  - (Box 65)
    - Stan, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2077-2078)
    - Stan II, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2079-2081)
    - Church office stills, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2082)
    - Historical Society, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2083-2085)
    - Church guy, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2086)
    - Birth of an Empire 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2087)
    - Paul 1, S.A. train car, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2088)
    - Train 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2089)
    - Saltair band, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2090)
    - Saltair, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2901-2093)
    - Saltair dub, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2094)
    - Saltair, 1984 August 18; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2095)
    - Saltair, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2096-2097)
    - S.A. Historic Society trip 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2098)
    - Saltair cover - sunset at Saltair, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2099)
    - Old Saltair production, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2100)
    - Old Saltair footage, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2101)
    - Cooking class 1and 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2102-2103)
    - Power appliances, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2104)
    - Power 2, 3, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2105-2106)
    - Math and science at Clearfield High (science 14), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2107)
    - Farm cover (genes 6), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2108)
    - Smart alarm (fuzzy 5 and 6), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2109-2110)
    - Rockwell (fuzzy 7), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2111)
    - Nevada test site (NTS) (nuke 7-9), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2112-2114)
    - Salt Flats - aerials, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2115)
    - Audio robot C-roll, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2116)
      Drive and lab worker
    - Salt Flats (fast 1), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2117)
    - Salt Flats - biker (fast 4), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2118)
    - Speed 6 September, old photos, Mary at City Council (fast 23), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2119)
    - Oil pumps (oil 8), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2120)
    - Oil field cover (oil 9), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2121)
    - JA's music robot, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2122)
    - Robots 2-5, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2123-2126)
    - Robots 9-12, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2127-2130)
    - Lab cover - robot 21, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2131)
    - School 3 - University of Utah classroom, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2132)
    - Hold DV 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2133)
    - Old cars (cars 4, 5), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2134-2135)
    - Cars - Mercedes detail (cars 6), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2136)
    - Rose Parade preparations, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2137)
    - KTVX: Movie world images, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2138)
    - Cruise night, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2139)
    - Farm boy, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2140-2142)
  - (Box 66)
    - Salt Flats 1, 2, 5, 6, 7, 9, 10, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2143-2149)
    - Bikes - Tonight Show stuff, show room, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2150)
    - Bikes - club ride, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2151)
    - Bikes - track, canyon, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2152)
    - Bikes - track, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2153)
    - Bikers 7, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2154)
    - Bikes - magic hour, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2155)
    - Bikes - Karl, cemetery, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2156)
    - Bikes - Canyon Cruzers, Slugs, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2157)
    - Bikes - training course (bikes 6), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2158)
    - Bikes in canyon -(camera mount), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2159)
    - Bikes in canyon - on bike (camera mount), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2160)
    - Bikes - drags (bikes 4), undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2161)
    - Bikers 6, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2162)
    - Tanning salon - Dr. Urban J. Andersch, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2163-2165)
    - Golden Rod film, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2166)
    - Fish genes, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2167)
    - Housing - Janette Fronit, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2168)
    - Wetland birds 4, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2169)
    - Bikers studio, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2170)
    - Old home pictures - Historical Society, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2171)
    - Green Hornet for KTVH - dub with Dolby off, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2172)
    - Lots of creases, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2173)
    - Horse shoe, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2174)
    - Spinner, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2175)
    - Urban legends - drive home: "The Hook", undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2176)
    - Restaurants - Eat; Benihana, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2177)
    - Old car show, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2178)
    - Bunny wash, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2179)
    - Franklin Field, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2180)
    - Mayor at Ball Park, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2181)
    - Byron Davis - table tennis, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2182)
    - Moab, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2183)
    - Hook lovers, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2184)
    - Swish pans 2, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2185)
    - Track for Salt Lake, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2186)
    - Bonsai, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2187)
    - Pump, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2188)
    - Exper., undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2189)
    - Streamliner, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2190)
    - 16mm 57 to be determined, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2191)
    - Autos - big car shot, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2192)
    - Speed - fast, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2193)
    - Bikes - street bikes, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2194)
    - Autos, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2195)
    - Motorcycle race, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2196)
    - Taco Bell 1, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2197)
    - Q Doctors, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2198)
    - Tele-Doctor University of Utah Medical, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2199)
    - Classified scam, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2200)
    - Girl found, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2201)
    - NKE United States transplant, 1996; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2202)
    - Games highlights, undated; Betacam videocassette (Cassette 2203)